[{"answer": "I go where I will and I do what I must.  That's why I'm in trouble. I'm sort've what you might call... 'in exile'", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " An honest man is always in trouble, my friend. Remember that", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Keep still", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Fine! You do it, my friend! I don't care", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend, just take him to the hospital, will ya", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " my friend, you go to the hospital with my friend right now, do hear me", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Do you find me attractive", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I look young for my age, don't I", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I look young for my age, don't I", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "How old do you think I am", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "How old do you think I am", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " How young", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You look young", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I don't know. Young", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Uhm. Look, ah... I'm the editor of the high school newspaper now and..", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "One of the editors, and we..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Who cares what you think", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "A wel", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend, I can't work under these conditions", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Get a life", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What do you mean you don't know why you bother? You bother because you know the poem is excellent", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Of course you do", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "He's afraid that his reputation will prevent people from giving my work an honest chance", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "As a writer", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I'm here to see Mr. my friend", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I'm not a plumber. Or a messenger. I was once a garbage man. But now I'm a poet", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Hey, my friend, I found Pearl wandering around by the garbage dump", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Who lost", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I, my friend, take you, my friend to be my wife", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "And do promise before God and these witnesses..", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "And do promise before God and these witnesses..", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "To be your loving and faithful husband", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "To be your loving and faithful husband", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "In plenty and in want", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "In plenty and in want", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "In joy and in sorrow", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "In joy and in sorrow", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "In sickness and in health", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "In joy and in sorrow", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "In sickness and in health", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "In sickness and in health", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "For as long as we both shall live", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well, that could be better. But it is a hundred thousand dollars up front. Guaranteed money. You could use that", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Of course it's good", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "No. Really, my friend. Don't", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I'm saying... my friend didn't like it", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "We gotta have rock 'n' roll shows these days, my friend. The poetry readings just don't pay the bills no more", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Did you hear about my friend? It was on the news today", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "What are you doing here, my friend", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": " Some what", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "I was here first", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "You go home", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": " It is true your husband served seven years in prison for statutory rape", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "And when was that", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yes. It is", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "That was... I dunno. Fifteen... Sixteen years ago", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "And when was that", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "And when were you married", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "That was... I dunno. Fifteen... Sixteen years ago", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "We were married seven years ago", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "And when were you married", "docId": "Henry-Fool.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Were you aware at all of the victim's relationship with his daughter", "qsentId": 62}]